I was heard because I'm elected, I'm on the Appropriations Committee, and I know what to do.
And they know that I know, and they know that that was wrong, and they were trying to get around the committee that I'm the ranking member of.
So I caught them, and I keep doing that over and over.
And now that's not hitting the press, so I'm glad I'm able to share it with you.
But just know when I say do the work, and I'm not nuancing this.
I'm just telling you what I've been doing, and I understand the frustration, and I understand the anger.
And I understand all of this because I've been in this longer than most people.
If you've been in this so long, that sounds so exhausting.
No.
How do you?
No?
No, I'm a Black woman.
Hey, in the Black church, what?
I ain't no way tired, come too far from where I started from.
Nobody told me the road was going to be easy.
I didn't come this far from him to leave me.
I'm just telling you, okay?
So now I'm not exhausted.